trygames.com 2007-05-05

# Trygames.com Privacy

The privacy of your information is important to us. The following are the privacy policies of Trymedia Systems, Inc.

Trymedia will be collecting two types of information from you: we collect non-personal information every time you visit our Web site or communicate with us over the Internet; and we collect personal information from you only when you engage in a transaction, download software or join a subscription service on our site. We explain how we collect and use both types of information below.

**The Personal Information Collected**  
Personal information is information that is unique to you, such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone number and credit card number. The following are the ways in which we collect personal information:

  * **Transaction Information**  
In order to complete a software purchase, you will be asked to share with us information required to complete the transaction successfully, such as billing and shipping addresses, credit card number and expiration date, etc.

  * **Subscription Information**  
You have the opportunity to receive our special software offers via e-mail. When you sign up for this service, you will be asked to provide us with your e-mail address.

  * **Download Information**  
Each software download started by you generates a unique serial number. If you purchase a license to a product, the serial number will be used to protect the copyright of the software and prevent piracy.

**How Personal Information Is Used**  
When you make a purchase, we use your information in the following ways:

  * Your personal information will be shared with third parties involved in facilitating or completing the transaction (for example, credit card authorization companies, the publisher of the software and, if applicable, the owner of the Web site that you were visiting when you clicked on a promotion for the software you are downloading).

  * Trymedia will send you, from time to time, email or mail on topics, including: (i) information regarding your purchase, such as news of software patches or updates; (ii) news regarding updates to our Web sites; and (iii) details regarding any special promotions sponsored by Trymedia, such as rebates, sweepstakes and gift promotions.

If you opt-in to a subscription or mailing list then Trymedia and the third parties described above who receive your information will use your information in the following ways:

  * Trymedia will send you emails and mail on special promotions that we believe will be valuable to you, including e-mails promoting special software deals, sponsored by Trymedia or third parties.

  * Third parties will send you emails and mail on special promotions that they believe are valuable to you.

  * Trymedia and third parties may conduct market research analysis in relation to mailing list subscribers.

We may also make the following general uses of your information:

  * We may use independent contractors to provide services on our behalf, for example credit card processing and market research analysis. These third parties may have access to your information in the course of providing these services on behalf of Trymedia. Any personal information we provide to such third parties is protected under confidentiality agreements.

  * We may disclose your personal information to authorities (i) if you violate our Terms of Use or any law, rule, or regulation, or (ii) if required by law or regulatory authority (for example, court order or subpoena).

  * In the event that Trymedia or certain of our assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

Use of your personal information by third party contractors when working on behalf of Trymedia shall be subject to our Privacy Policy. Use of your personal information by other third parties who receive your information will be in accordance with their privacy policies.

You may unsubscribe from Trymedia's promotional mailing list at anytime by following the unsubscribe instructions that appear in each email that you will receive from Trymedia. To unsubscribe from the mailing lists of third parties you will need to follow their stated unsubscribe processes.

Many questions regarding your purchase history and assistance with your software can be answered by visiting our [ Customer Support Center](http://csc.trymedia.com/csc/start/affiliate=trygames/lang=en). If you would like access to other information and records that Trymedia retains in relation to you please complete and submit the Trymedia Information Request Form which can be obtained by sending an email requesting the form to: [privacy@trymedia.com](mailto:privacy@trymedia.com). Please be aware that information will not be released in response to a request until Trymedia has received a completed request form, verified the authenticity of the request and received payment of the modest fee due for each request. Once you have received the information and records you have requested you may request that they be changed, updated or removed. However, you should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove or verify each and every record of the information you have provided to us and that any changes or deletions will not effect the information we have provided to third parties in accordance with this policy prior to such change or deletion. The need to back-up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate.

**What We Won't Do With Personal Information**  
Trymedia Systems, Inc. will not sell or rent your personal information to any third parties unconnected with your purchase of the software.

**Where Your Information is Used**  
When you provide us with your information you acknowledge that this information may be stored and processed on servers located any where in the World, including either inside or outside of the USA or the European Economic Area ("EEA"). You consent to your information being transferred outside the USA and EEA and being stored and processed at our discretion on any of our servers wherever located.

**Security**  
Because security is important to us, we exercise care in providing secure transmission of your personal information before it is transferred across the Internet from your personal computer to our secure servers. We use industry-standard, secure-socket-layer (SSL) technology, which is utilized by most popular browsers, including Netscape and Microsoft Explorer, to encrypt (or convert into code) most of your personal information before it is transferred across the Internet. To further safeguard your most sensitive credit card information, we transfer such information across the Internet in an encrypted format and then store such information in our databases.

Remember to close your browser window when you have finished a purchase in order to ensure that others cannot access your personal information.

We will permit only authorized employees, who are trained in the proper handling of personal data, to access your personal information.

To further protect your personal information, we have a security system that includes: firewall technologies; logical network segmentation, allowing restricted access to stored profile information; encryption; and logical and physical security restrictions to our databases and systems.

However, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet. There is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart our security systems. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**Other, Non-Personal Information Collected and Used**  
Like many other Internet sites, we automatically collect non-personal information regarding our visitors, such as software client information (for example, IP addresses, browser versions and operating systems) and aggregate information (for example, number of pages accessed) in order to analyze Web traffic and usage trends. Information of this nature does not pertain to your specific identity and is not associated with your personal information.

To enhance your experience on our Web pages, Trymedia and our third party advertiser(s) commonly employ Internet technologies, such as "cookies," to collect and store non-personal information about our visitors. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are transferred by a website and stored by your Web browser on your computer's hard drive. With most browsers, you can set the preferences to show a warning each time a cookie request is received. You can also set the browser not to accept cookies at all. However, because we won't be able to personalize your experience if we cannot recognize you, we suggest that you allow your browser to accept cookies.

Cookies and Web beacons (also called "pixel tags") may be used by Trymedia or our third party advertiser(s) to determine how you reached us, to track your usage patterns once you are on our Web pages or Web Site, and to target our Internet banner advertisements on our Web pages and Web sites.

We may also provide to third parties information about you that does not allow you to be identified or contacted, including where such information is combined with similar information about other users. For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of unique users who have purchased software from Trymedia and the demographic breakdown of our user community.

**What Is Not Covered By This Privacy Policy**  
Except as stated above, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices or policies of any third parties, such as companies or entities that we do not own or control, and does not apply to any links to sites that are not maintained by us, or to people that we do not employ or manage.

**Questions, Comments or Concerns**  
Many questions regarding your purchase history and assistance with your software can be answered by visiting our [ Customer Support Center](http://csc.trymedia.com/csc/start/affiliate=trygames/lang=en). If you have additional questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at either of the addresses below:

By email: [privacy@trymedia.com](mailto:privacy@trymedia.com)

By mail:  
Trymedia Systems, Inc.   
135 Main Street  
San Francisco, CA 94105  
Attention: Privacy and Legal Depts.

 **Privacy Policy Updates**  
This privacy policy has been in effect since March 15, 2005. We may, in our sole discretion, revise this Privacy Policy at any time; all such revisions shall be effective when posted on the [www.trygames.com](http://www.trygames.com/) Web site. If we change the way your personal information will be used, we will post an announcement on our homepage. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy in order to keep apprised of our current privacy practices.

BY USING OUR WEB SITE OR PURCHASING THE SOFTWARE YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OF US PROCESSING YOUR INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT USE OUR WEB SITE OR PURCHASE THE SOFTWARE.
